{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Radiant Panel Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40298/":{"taskOID":40298,"originalTaskOID":40298,"setID":598,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6952,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the radiant system being installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10207,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Individual room(s) of existing home","answerDisplayText":"Individual room(s) of existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10208,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New construction or addition","answerDisplayText":"New construction or addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10209,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Entire existing home","answerDisplayText":"Entire existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6951,"questionDisplayText":"Square Footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of the area the system will serve?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10205,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10206,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4794,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Panels","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kinds of panels are you considering? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2540,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor panels for heating","answerDisplayText":"Floor panels for heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2539,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Floor panels for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Floor panels for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1301,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ceiling panels for heating","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling panels for heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1300,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ceiling panels for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling panels for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6757,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall panels for heating","answerDisplayText":"Wall panels for heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6756,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall panels for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Wall panels for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6952,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the radiant system being installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10207,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Individual room(s) of existing home","answerDisplayText":"Individual room(s) of existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10208,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New construction or addition","answerDisplayText":"New construction or addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10209,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Entire existing home","answerDisplayText":"Entire existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10207,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Individual room(s) of existing home","answerDisplayText":"Individual room(s) of existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10208,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New construction or addition","answerDisplayText":"New construction or addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10209,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Entire existing home","answerDisplayText":"Entire existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6951,"questionDisplayText":"Square Footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of the area the system will serve?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10205,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10206,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10205,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1500 - 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10206,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 2500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4794,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Panels","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kinds of panels are you considering? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2540,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor panels for heating","answerDisplayText":"Floor panels for heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2539,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Floor panels for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Floor panels for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1301,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ceiling panels for heating","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling panels for heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1300,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ceiling panels for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling panels for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6757,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall panels for heating","answerDisplayText":"Wall panels for heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6756,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall panels for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Wall panels for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2540,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor panels for heating","answerDisplayText":"Floor panels for heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2539,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Floor panels for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Floor panels for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1301,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ceiling panels for heating","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling panels for heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1300,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ceiling panels for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling panels for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6757,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall panels for heating","answerDisplayText":"Wall panels for heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6756,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall panels for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Wall panels for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40298/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40298,"taskName":"Radiant Panel Heating Units - Install","taskDescription":"Install Radiant Panel Heating Units","xmTaskDescriptor":"Radiant Panel Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":191,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"HVAC Radiant Panel air ac","textMessagingName":"Install Radiant Panel","rolloverLongDesc":"Can also be mounted on ceilings. Designed to directly heat the objects in the room, including people, rather than heating the air. Powered by electricity.","rolloverShortDesc":"Hi-tech heating panels mounted on walls.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Radiant Panel Heating Units.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Radiant Heating Panel Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Radiant Panels \u0026 Units","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Radiant Panel Heat Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Radiant Panel Heating Units - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Radiant PanelHeating Project","urlName":"Radiant-Panel-Heating-Units-Install","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Radiant Heating Panel Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"radiant panel heating, space heater, wall mounted","emcCategoryOid":-12040,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":598,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}